The setup team can come up
with ideas for the interior decor.
For outfits, maybe coordinate one thing with
the costume team and leave the rest to them.
The food team will decide the menu.
Please come up with a budget for snacks,
drinks, and... oh, also disposable utensils.
We can decide on the café rules later.
Once each team has an estimate,
we'll turn in our budget proposal
to the student council.
So thanks and do your best, everyone!
All right!
Okay!
Got it.
I guess that's all for today.
Okay, dismissed!
Thank you!
Thanks!
I'm getting excited!
Hold on a sec.
Think this'll work?
Thanks!
Hey, since we're done early,
wanna go do karaoke?
Oh, the place by the station?
Yeah.
Sounds fun! Let's go, let's go!
Guys, wanna go do karaoke?
You wanna go, too, Saki?
Yeah!
Let's do it!
All right!
Um, I'm sorry. I have some errands to run.
Yeah? Maybe next time, then.
Yeah. Sorry. Bye.
See you later!
Adios!
Shinjo! Too bad, man.
Yeah, whatever.
A stepbrother is really
nothing more than a stranger.
And that's perfectly normal, because even
if we suddenly become siblings one day,
we have no shared experience living together.
People say that strangers
all begin as siblings first,
but in the case of stepsiblings,
they start off as strangers and
stay strangers until the very end.
That's what I used to think.
Episode 10 "Relations and Regrets"
I'm back.
Welcome home!
Oh, are you okay for time?
Yes. I called in and let them know,
so I don't have to rush.
For real?
You said we needed to talk about the
parent-teacher meeting, so I hurried home.
Sorry about that.
If it didn't have to be in person,
you could've just messaged me.
I guess so.
But I didn't think text would get everything
across, and I wanted to be sure, you know?
Yeah, sure... I guess?
How are things going with Yuta-kun at school?
How are things?
We're in different classes,
so pretty much the same as ever.
No one at school knows that
you're brother and sister, right?
No, I don't think so.
We haven't really been telling anyone.
What's the matter? Didn't you want to talk
about my parent-teacher meeting?
The truth is that Taichi-san
is extremely busy right now.
I don't want to put even more pressure on him.
So I was thinking of going
to both of your meetings.
But since my bar is so small,
I can't really take multiple days off.
But if I do both meetings
back-to-back on the same day,
the other kids would find
out that you're siblings.
Well, that's not the only reason.
Asamura
Ayase
I'm back.
Welcome home!
Welcome home, Big Brother.
What perfect timing.
Huh?
We were just talking about what to do
for your parent-teacher meeting.
Huh? Mine?
Yes.
Taichi-san is extremely busy right now,
so I'm planning to go to both of yours.
Huh?
I've thought about it,
and if you and Saki can schedule yours
for different days, we'll make it work.
Huh?
Well, you haven't told anyone at school
that you're brother and sister, right?
So that would be safer than me
going to both on the same day.
You mean you'd go all the way
out to our school twice?
Yes, that's right.
But my dad isn't the only busy one here.
You work nights at the bar.
Isn't it already hard enough for you just
to come to our school in the afternoon?
I'll be fine!
But still...
I've got to get going.
Let's go over the details later.
Oh, okay...
I'm off!
See you later...
Ayase-san?
I have to get to work.
See you later.
See you.
Well, that's not the only reason.
I don't feel like Yuta-kun
accepts me as his mother yet,
and that makes me a little sad.
I'm back.
Welcome home, Ayase-san.
Good timing. Want to eat together?
Sure.
So, about the parent-teacher meeting...
Why don't we eat while we talk?
Yeah.
Thanks for the meal. It was delicious.
Glad you liked it.
You're getting better at cooking.
Thanks.
So, about those meetings...
Yeah.
We don't want people to know
we're brother and sister,
but that's really just for us.
I have been thinking it's kind of selfish.
I don't actually have a problem with
people knowing that you're my sister.
But I know that's not for just me to decide.
I feel the same way.
This isn't a decision I can make alone.
But I've seen what happens
when my mom works too hard
and the toll it starts to take on her health.
Yeah.
I don't want to make things any harder
for my dad or for Akiko-san.
Then we have our decision.
Let's schedule our meetings for the same day.
That way, Akiko-san only
has to go to school once.
Yeah.
Ayase-san?
This isn't only because
it's hard on her, though.
There are other reasons...
that I want my mom to go
to both of our meetings.
But I'll tell her what we decided.
Oh... Sure.
Thanks for dinner. It was good.
I'll take care of that.
I'm sure you're tired from work.
Then let's do it together.
This is good.
This should make them both happy.
This isn't fair. It just isn't, Asamura-kun.
I know that Dad and Akiko-san
really want us to get along.
The fact that you're worried
about how hard my mom works
makes me really happy.
That's why I have to control my feelings.
I have to put a lid on them and seal them away.
I'm trying so hard to erase these feelings,
but I'm so touched by such a tiny gesture...
We aren't strangers anymore.
Asamura-kun is my stepbrother.
Ayase-san is my stepsister.
We're family.
Friday, September 4th
Are you sure about this?
Ayase-san and I talked and
made the decision together.
It feels unnatural to keep hiding
the fact that we're siblings.
Besides, aren't you super busy right now, Dad?
Well, yeah.
I'm sure Akiko-san will be
happy about this, though.
She said something to me...
"I want us to be a real family.
It shouldn't be too hard."
"Otherwise, what's the point of building
relations by marrying?" Her words.
If Akiko-san knew you accepted
her as part of your family,
it would make her very happy.
Yeah.
Good morning, Dad. Big Brother.
Good morning, Saki-chan!
Good morning, Ayase-san.
I'm sorry I didn't make breakfast.
Oh, that's okay! Why don't you eat with us?
All right.
Here, Big Brother.
It made Mom really happy.
Told you!
Good morning, Dad.
Good morning, Saki-chan!
It made Mom really happy.
"Mom."
You don't say...
Well, that explains a lot.
Yeah.
I was surprised when you were asking
about Ayase, but now it all makes sense.
But this means I said some nasty stuff
about your sister. Sorry, man.
You had no way of knowing. It's fine.
I was totally convinced
you'd fallen for Ayase-san.
Oh, come on.
I know. Sorry. I shouldn't make
careless assumptions.
But the way things are going,
it seems like you get on fine as siblings.
Well, yeah.
Good, good.
Isn't that kind of an uneven trade?
It's fine, it's fine!
Oh, that looks good!
Ah! And your salmon looks tasty, Yumicchi!
Only if you'll trade me for some
of that secret family recipe karaage.
You've got yourself a deal!
Hey.
You guys wanna hang out again later this month?
Hey, great idea!
Where should we go? And when?
How about bowling?
Let's find a day everyone's free.
Sounds good.
Oh, bowling? It's been a while.
What do you think?
Um...
Do you have to work? Or study?
I don't think I have any shifts scheduled.
But I always study on days I don't work.
Oh, no wonder.
Ah. So what should we do, then?
Then how about a study session?
Uh, like we all meet up somewhere?
Yeah.
How about the library?
In that case, how about at my meowse?
My parents always take my
brothers out, so no problemo!
Come meow'n over!
Awesome!
Than it's settled!
Thanks, Narasaka-san.
Yeah, thanks!
All good!
That work for you, Saki?
Sure.
Yeah, totally! When I took my brothers
to the pool, it was a disaster!
They were out of control!
Once they start playing,
they don't pay attention to anything else!
That's a big sister for you.
So are we your little brothers now, too?
I mean, we did kinda go nuts.
Yeah, for sure. Sometimes you
just want to show off, right?
No way. That's why you guys are still children.
Dang!
That's why I'd rather date an older guy.
Okay, you're little brothers one,
o, and three! There ya go!
Number three!
And you'll be my straitlaced little sis, Saki.
Come on, hurry up!
Your big sister just might spoil you!
I don't want a sister like that.
Wow, you really meant that!
Sorry, that was my honest reaction.
I feel so attacked!
You sure look down, my sweet junior.
Navigator
When You're Searching for a Book
Rewards Points Promotion
Earn up to 30%
You haven't had many shifts
with Saki-chan lately.
Are you starting to miss her?
Senpai, if you aren't careful, a laugh like
that might turn the masses against you.
There, there, young man.
Just tell your big sis here
what's been troubling you.
Come now, open your heart and
nestle your poor little self in my bosom!
That's not the problem at all, though.
We're brother and sister.
There's no way things are like that.
Like what, exactly?
Like me being lonely because I don't
get to work with my little sister.
Not a chance.
I mean, she's only your stepsister, right?
Either way, she's still my sister.
What a conventional response.
How uninteresting.
This isn't a matter of how interesting it is.
Hmph. Then perhaps I'll cheer my gloomy
junior up with an exciting news flash.
My college is holding an open campus
event soon. You should come!
When you find yourself surrounded by pretty
older girls, I'm sure you'll cheer up.
You go to a women's college, don't you?
Why, yes.
S H I B U Y A   C E N T E R
Can I help you find something?
Oh. Um, didn't I see you in the summer class?
Yes, you did.
Do you still go to that
cram school, Asamura-san?
Yeah, I do. But only on weekends.
Wait, "Asamura-san"?
Oh.
I'm Fujinami Kaho.
Kaho as in "summer" and "sail."
"Sale"?
"Sail" as in sailing, not selling.
That's usually enough to explain to
people the kanji for writing my name.
Oh, like the sail on a boat.
See? You got it now, right?
Nice to meet you.
Likewise.
Oh, I didn't mean to interrupt
your work. See you.
Oh, no trouble.
Whoa! The miso soup
sure tastes different today.
Is it strange?
No, no, it's good!
I bet Yuta will like it, too.
I'm glad to hear that.
Yeah, that's good! This is true happiness.
Dad, would you like seconds?
Please!
All right.
Dinner for my big brother
If I really wanted to keep
my distance from him,
I wouldn't make him dinner.
I wouldn't leave a note.
That might be the best way to act.
But I start to wonder, and it makes me worry...
Wouldn't that be more like breaking
ties than keeping my distance?
I don't really want to go that far.
I don't want to avoid him completely.
And now, I'm sure it would be even harder
than when we were strangers anyway.
Am I going to wind up with regrets
about how things turned out?
I don't even know.
Episode 11 "Brother and Sister"